If anyone asks.
We're the Millers is a comedy, crime film directed by Rawson Marshall Thurber.
A veteran pot dealer creates a fake family as part of his plan
to move a huge shipment of weed into the U.S.
from Mexico.
Rose O'Reilly, played by Jennifer Aniston.
David Clark, played by Jason Sudeikis.
Casey Mathis, played by Emma Roberts.
Kenny Rossmore, played by Will Poulter.
Brad Gurdlinger, played by Ed Helms.
Don Fitzgerald, played by Nick Offerman.
We're the Millers is a 2013 road black comedy film directed by Rawson Marshall Thurber and starring Jennifer Aniston,
Jason Sudeikis, Emma Roberts, Will Poulter, Nick Offerman, Kathryn Hahn, Molly Quinn, and Ed Helms.
The film's screenplay was written by Bob Fisher, Steve Faber, Sean
Anders, and John Morris, based on a story by Fisher and Faber.
The plot follows a small-time pot dealer (Sudeikis) who convinces his neighbors to help him by
pretending to be his family in order to smuggle drugs from Mexico into the United States.
The film premiered at the Traverse City Film Festival on August 3,
2013 and was released on August 7, 2013, by Warner Bros.
Despite mixed reviews, it was a box office success, grossing $270 million
worldwide against a $37 million budget during its theatrical run.
It was nominated for four People's Choice Awards, and
six MTV Movie Awards, winning two.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, mexico,
drug smuggling, fireworks, camping.
The tone is lighthearted.